(Sheldon:)Oh, there's my missing neutrino.
(Sheldon:)You were hiding from me
as an unbalanced charge...
(Sheldon:)...weren't you,
you little subatomic dickens?
- Hi, Sheldon.
- Hey, look, I found my missing neutrino.
(Howard:)Oh, good,
we can take it off the milk carton.
We're gonna apologize to Raj
and invite him out to dinner.
Apologize? For what?
(Leonard:)He came over last night with some pretty
good news and we weren't very supportive.
(Sheldon:)I sense you're trying
to tell me something.
(Howard:)You were a colossal asshat.
Oh, no, I beg to differ.
(Sheldon:)Of the three of us,
I was by far the most supportive.
Really? Do tell.
(Sheldon:)How will Raj ever reach true greatness
if his friends lower the bar for him?
When I was 11, my sister bought our father
a "world's greatest dad" coffee mug.
(Sheldon:)And frankly, the man coasted
until the day he died.